janeapp.com 2017-02-05

# Privacy Policy | Jane - Clinic Management Software

_Date last modified: July 30, 2013_

JANE respects your privacy and we appreciate your interest in our organization. This Privacy Policy covers our collection, use and disclosure of information we collect through our website [www.janeapp.com](http://www.janefinder.com/) our software as a service JANE (collectively referred to in this Policy as our “Digital Properties”). The use of information collected through our service shall be limited to the purpose of providing the service(s) for which you have engaged JANE. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. 

## Information Related to Data Collected from You

### Information we collect and how it is used

On certain pages, we give users the option of providing us with contact information or account registration information, including name, phone, and e-mail address, as a requirement If you choose to purchase a service from us we will collect information from you such as credit card number and billing name and address. Providing this information is voluntary which we use internally. All information collected while within the JANE Digital Properties shall hereby be referred to as (“Collected Information”).

Information you provide may be used by JANE for marketing purposes, including but not limited to, one-off promotional e-mailing, direct mail, and sales contacts. We will honor all requests for list removal sent to [seejanerun@janeapp.com](mailto:seejanerun@janeapp.com). 

### Service Providers

We use other third parties such as credit card processing companies to bill you for services, a support provider to help us collect feedback and manage our support and an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf. When you sign up for our services, we will share your Collected Information only as necessary for the third party to provide that service.

### Access to Personal Information

If you’re Collected Information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, and delete/deactivate it by logging into your account and making the appropriate changes or by emailing our customer support at [support@janeapp.com](mailto:support@janeapp.com). 

### Tracking Technologies

JANE employs, or our third party advertising partners employ, various tracking technologies, such as cookies, web beacons and analytics software, that help us better manage content on our Digital Properties by informing us what content is effective.

### Cookies

When you visit our Digital Properties we send one or more “cookies” to your computer or other devices. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers stored on your computer through your web browser and are used by most websites to help personalize your web experience. Some cookies may facilitate additional site features for enhanced performance and functionality such as remembering preferences, allowing social interactions, analyzing usage for site optimization, providing custom content, allowing third parties to provide social sharing tools, and serving images or videos from third party websites. Some features on this site will not function if you do not allow cookies. We may link the information we store in cookies to any Collected Information you submit while on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies enable us to track and target the interest of our users to enhance the experience on our site. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser’s “help” file.

**Functional cookies** , persistent and session type, store information to enable core site functionality, such as Live Chat and Client ID remembrance. 

**Analytics cookies** allow us to count page visits and traffic sources so we can measure and improve the performance of our site and our marketing campaigns. 

**Advertising cookies** may be set through our website by our advertising partners. Data may be collected by these companies that enable them to serve up advertisements on other sites that are relevant to your interests. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but some features on the site will not function properly.

### Web Beacons

JANE uses Web Beacons alone or in conjunction with cookies to compile information about our Digital Properties. Web Beacons are tiny graphic object that are embedded in a web page or email and is usually invisible to the user but allows checking that a user has viewed the page or email. Web Beacons may be used within the Digital Properties to track email open rates, web page visits or form submissions. In some cases, we tie the information gathered by Web Beacons to our customers’ Collected Information. For example, we use clear gifs in our HTML-based emails to let us know which emails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns.

**Third Party Tracking Technologies** The use of cookies and web beacons by any tracking utility company or third party service provider is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. 

### Analytics Software

We and our third party tracking-utility partners use log files on our Digital Properties to gather certain information automatically and store it for analytical purposes. This information includes internet protocol (“IP”) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information to track and aggregate no-personal information to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements around our Digital Properties and to gather demographic information about our user base as a in the aggregate.

### Social Media Features and Widgets

Our Digital Properties include social media features, such as the Facebook Like button and widgets, such as the Share this button or interactive mini-programs that run on our site. These features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on our site, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Social Media Features and Widgets are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Digital Properties. Your interactions with these Features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.

### Facebook Connect and Twitter

You can log in to our some of our services using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an Open ID provider such as Twitter. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

### Testimonials, Ratings and Reviews

We post customer testimonials on our Digital Properties which may contain Collected Information. We obtain the customer's consent via email prior to posting the testimonial and attaching the users name along with their testimonial. If you want your testimonial removed, please contact us at [testimonial@janeapp.com](mailto:testimonial@janeapp.com). 

We also partner with a third party service provider to collect and display ratings and review content on our web site. If the content collected by the third party for display includes personally identifiable information, it will be rejected and will not be posted unless explicit consent is provided by the customer.

## Information Related to Data Collected for our Subscribers

The following terms shall have the definitions contained below.

Subscriber shall mean the business or entity that purchased a subscription the JANE Software as a Service via entering into the JANE Software Service Agreement (“SSA”).

Customer shall mean the businesses or individuals scheduling and purchasing products and services from SUBSCRIBER.

### Service Provider Collection and Use

JANE collects information under the direction of its Subscribers, and has no direct relationship with the individuals whose personal data it processes.

### Choice

JANE collects information for our Subscribers. If you are a Customer of one of our Subscribers and would no longer like to be contacted by one of our Subscribers that use our service, please contact the Subscriber that you interact with directly.

### Service Provider, Sub-Processors/Ownward Transfer

JANE may transfer Collected Information to third parties that help us provide our service. Transfers to these third parties are covered by the provisions in this Policy regarding notice and choice and the service agreements with our Subscribers.

### Access to Data Controlled by our Subscribers

JANE has no direct relationship with the Customers whose personal data it processes. A Customer who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his query to the Subscriber. If the Subscriber requests JANE to remove the data, we will respond to their request within 30 business days.

## Additional Information

### Legal Disclosure

We reserve the right to disclose the Collected Information upon the following circumstances: 

  * As required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena, or similar legal process.
  * when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.
  * To any other third party with your prior consent to do so.
  * If JANE is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your Collected Information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information.

### Data Retention

We will retain your Collected Information and the Collected Information we process on behalf of our Subscribers for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you and our Subscribers services. We will retain and use this information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

### Security of your Information

The security of personal information is a high priority at JANE. We maintain our Digital Properties and all associated data with technical, administrative and physical safeguards to protect against loss, unauthorized access, destruction, misuse, modification and improper disclosure. When you enter sensitive information (such as a credit card number) on our order forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard. JANE is committed to providing reasonable and appropriate security controls to protect our web sites and their information against foreseeable hazards. If you have any questions about security on our web site, you can contact us at [privacy@janeapp.com](mailto:privacy@janeapp.com). 

### Changes to this Privacy Policy

JANE reserves the right to change this Privacy Statement. JANE will provide notification of the material changes to this Privacy Policy through notifications on the main page of this site or via email at least thirty (30) business days prior to the change taking effect.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions regarding this Privacy Statement you can contact us via email at [privacy@janeapp.com](mailto:privacy@janeapp.com) or via postal mail at: 

Jane Software Inc.   
Unit 201 - 173 Forester St.   
North Vancouver, BC, V7H 0A6   
Canada   
844-310-5263
